

CJIES TAN

FRONT END DEVELOPER

CONTACT

Name:

Xi Jie Tan

Fmail:

cijies@gmail.com

Phone:

+886-978-109-929

Website:

https://cjies.com

EDUCATION

Computer Science B.Eng

National Cheng Kung University Tainan, Taiwan (2010 - 2014) Major in web development and UI design.

Science Class

Pay Fong High School Melaka, Malaysia (2004 - 2009) Societies: Multimedia Society

SKILLS

Web Developement

React, Angular, Ionic, Django, Sass

Design

Branding, RWD design, Sketch

Languages

Mandarin, English, Japanese, Cantonese, Malay

PROFILE



HELLO,

my name is CJ, I am a software engineer and web developer with over three years of experience in Taipei. Specializes in front end development with react/redux, angularJS and hybrid application. Loves to write code in high-paced and challenging environment to deliver high-quality and maintainable product.

EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer

iCHEF Co. Ltd., Taipei

Mar 2016 - Present

- Developed a web CMS application for restaurant POS.
- Designed and coded a large in-house component library for react apps.
- Created a cross-platform deploy tool to deliver products easier and faster.
- Organized Taipei F2E&RGBA meetup every month.
- Participated in many community-organized meetups to sharing experiences and new findings.

Tech skills: React/Redux, Django, Electron, Docker, etc

Front End Engineer

Sep 2014 - Feb 2016

Galaxy Software Services, Taipei

- Positioned as main front-end engineer in design team.
- Architectured a common build scripts for web development.
- Developed Taipei 1999 mobile application (iOS & Android).
- Optimized and tuned web performance in mobile platforms.
- Worked with software developers from different departments to build large software applications.

Tech skills: Ionic, AngularJS, Cordova, Kendo, .net MVC Joined projects: Payroll System, Document System, Government Projects

E-TOP Project Web Designer

Jun 2013 - Jul 2014

Computer & Network Center NCKU, Tainan

- Designed website UI.
- Customized Kendo framework's stylesheet.

Tech skills: Kendo, Sass, Codelgniter (PHP)